Karan Chourasia

An independent self-motivated graduate with proven and tested negotiation, communication, and writing skills. With more than 2 years of experience in the content writing field, I broaden the boundary of my knowledge constantly and work as efficiently as possible.

House No. 4, Kabirdih, Topchanchi, Dhanbad (828402) 9523775339 dark.1karan@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Bluebird Solutions, Ahmedabad — *Visa Application Writer*

March 2023 - PRESENT

Working freelance, I have drafted more than 100 Visa SOPs based on the client's personalized requirements.

Allen Overseas, Kota — Content Sales Closer

March 2022 - March 2023

I worked as a freelancer subject specialist, describing offshore courses best suited for international students.

Sudypool.com, Online — Subject Matter Specialist

July 2021 - March 2023

Worked as a freelance writer as a subject matter specialist for Social Science subjects, it worked on an online bidding basis.

EDUCATION

Banaras Hindu University, Varanasi — B.A. (Political Science)

July 2019 - September 2022

Completed my Bachelor's degree from one of the most reputed institutions in India, core subjects included English, Economics, Political Science, History, Sociology, and Computer Basics.

Delhi Public School, Dhanbad — HSC (I.Com)

April 2015 - March 2017

It was a wholesome experience to receive education from one of India's most prominent schooling brands.

PROJECTS

Madad-e-aawam — Fundraising Campaign

Worked as the Secretary cum co-founder of the campaign named

SKILLS

MS Office

Creative Writing

Content Writing

Leadership Skills (Served as Director of Interact Club for 3 years)

Strong Communication

Public Speaking

Sales

Interests

Blogging

Writing

Music

Poetry

Reading

Start-ups

LANGUAGES

English

(Indian/British/American)

Hindi

Urdu

German

'madad-e-aawam' which helped 500 families amidst Covid phase one to receive groceries, sanitary pads, and other mandatory life support.